A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13 FA285
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Titles, 9
  - "Longitudinal Studies of Child Personality: Abstracts with Index" - Permissions and Production, September 17, 1957-July 15, 1959 (Box 98, Folder 1175)
  - "Man, Mind and Medicine", November 16, 1966-January 16, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1176)
  - "Maternal Deaths, The Ways to Prevention", February 3, 1933-October 26, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 1177)
  - "Maternity Care in a Rural Community", March 3, 1938-August 15, 1938 (Box 98, Folder 1178)
  - "Maternity Care in Two Countries", November 12, 1948-December 28, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 1179)
  - "The Meaning of Social Medicine", October 19, 1953-September 20, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 1180)
  - "The Meaning of Social Medicine", October 19, 1953-September 20, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 1181)
  - "Medical Addenda", November 16, 1944-July 10, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 1182)
  - "Medical Care of the Discharged Hospital Patient", December 18, 1942-August 8, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 1183)
  - "Medical Education and the Changing Order", November 15, 1944-August 13, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 1184)
  - "Medical Education in Japan", August 22, 1963-August 30, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 1185)
  - "Medical Education in Japan", August 22, 1963-August 30, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 1186)
  - "Medical Research Review", 1953, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 1187)
  - "Medical Services by Government", July 27, 1945-March 25, 1949 (Box 100, Folder 1188)
  - "Medical Services for Rural Areas" - Correspondence and Distribution, February 8, 1956-November 25, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 1189)
  - "Medical Services for Rural Areas" - Editorial and Production, May 10, 1956-April 10, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 1190)
  - "Medicine and the Neuroses", May 29, 1945-December 12, 1945 (Box 100, Folder 1191)
  - "Medicine in Industry", April 21, 1945-June 30, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 1192)
  - "Medicine in the Changing Order", January 29, 1946-December 16, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 1193)
  - Memo Sheets, November 1951 (Box 100, Folder 1194)
  - Memorials, 1934-1962 (Box 100, Folder 1195)
  - "Mental Health in College", June 26, 1935-November 29, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 1196)
  - "Mental Health in Modern Society" - Correspondence, May 8, 1944-July 16, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 1197)
  - "Mental Health in Modern Society" - Distribution and Printing, February 7, 1947-December 16, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 1198)
  - "Mental Health in the United States" - Correspondence and Distribution, October 25, 1960-November 20, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 1199)
  - "Mental Health in the United States" - Editorial and Production, January 9, 1961-October 11, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 1200)
  - "Mental Health Through Education" - Correspondence, October 28, 1933-January 21, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 1201)
  - "Mental Health Through Education" - Correspondence - Printing-Ryan, 1935-1938, 1947-1950 (Box 101, Folder 1202)
  - "Mental Hygiene and Social Work", April 20, 1929-June 27, 1946 (Box 101, Folder 1203)
  - "Mental Illness: A Guide for the Family" - Circularizing and Distribution, February 3, 1944-January 31, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 1204)
  - "Mental Illness: A Guide for the Family" - Correspondence, 1949-1951, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 1205)
  - "Mental Illness: A Guide for the Family" - Correspondence - Printing, February 3, 1942-November 1, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 1206)
  - "Mental Illness: A Guide for the Family" - First Edition - Printings 1-5, August 2, 1942-March 14, 1945 (Box 102, Folder 1207)
  - "Mental Illness: A Guide for the Family" - Paper Edition - Printings 1-6, December 12, 1944-August 12, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 1208)
  - "Metabolic Homeostasis" - Correspondence and Distribution, January 17, 1958-September 13, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 1209)
  - "Metabolic Homeostasis" - Editorial and Production, March 9, 1959-November 20, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 1210)
  - "Metabolic Response to Neonatal Surgery" - Correspondence and Distribution, October 10, 1955-May 5, 1958 (Box 102, Folder 1211)
  - "Metabolic Response to Neonatal Surgery" - Editorial and Production, January 10, 1956-June 19, 1956 (Box 102, Folder 1212)
  - "Microbial Antagonisms and Antibiotic Substances" - Correspondence, May 28, 1943-May 5, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 1213)
  - "Microbial Antagonisms and Antibiotic Substances" - Printing, July 1, 1944-February 14, 1946 (Box 102, Folder 1214)
  - "Microbial Antagonisms and Antibiotic Substances" - Revised Edition, August 22, 1945-May 6, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 1215)
  - "Milk and Food Sanitation Practice" - Correspondence, May 13, 1942-November 7, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 1216)
  - "Milk and Food Sanitation Practice" - Distribution and Printing, December 18, 1946-February 8, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1217)
  - "Modern Attack on Tuberculosis" - Correspondence, 1935-1951, 1957-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1218)
  - "Modern Attack on Tuberculosis" - Printing, May 1, 1942-December 16, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 1219)
  - "Mosquito Control" - Correspondence, February 18, 1938-September 23, 1943 (Box 103, Folder 1220)
  - "Mosquito Control" - Printing, 1940-1944, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 1221)
  - "Mosquito Control" Revised Edition - Correspondence, May 11, 1943-February 15, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 1222)
  - "Mosquito Control" Revised Edition - Printing, December 27, 1943-May 2, 1946 (Box 104, Folder 1223)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports), November 9, 1964-August 4, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 1224)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports), November 9, 1964-August 4, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 1225)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports), November 9, 1964-August 4, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 1226)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports) - Reports, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 1227)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports) - Reports, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 1228)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports) - Reports, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 1229)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports) - Reports, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 1230)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports) - Reports, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1231)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports) - Reports, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1232)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services (Subsidy for Harvard University Press Publication of Reports) - Reports, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1233)
  - "Negroes and Medicine" - Correspondence, 1955-1958, 1967-1970 (Box 105, Folder 1234)
  - "Negroes and Medicine" - Distribution and Editorial, October 17, 1957-January 22, 1959 (Box 105, Folder 1235)
  - "Negroes and Medicine" - Permission to Quote and Production, September 3, 1957-October 23, 1958 (Box 105, Folder 1236)
  - "Negroes and Medicine" - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., 1951-1958, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 1237)
  - "Nephrons and Kidneys", April 19, 1965-July 15, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 1238)
  - "Nephrons and Kidneys" - Complimentary Distribution, December 15, 1968-June 30, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 1239)
  - "Neural Mechanisms in Poliomyelitis", March 14, 1940-April 3, 1944 (Box 106, Folder 1240)
  - New Mexico Forms, January 31, 1952-February 5, 1952 (Box 106, Folder 1241)
  - Newsletter, December 5, 1929-June 30, 1947 (Box 106, Folder 1242)
  - "New Opportunities for Negroes in Medicine", December 7, 1961-November 22, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 1243)
  - "Nursing and Nursing Education", April 4, 1945-March 30, 1949 (Box 106, Folder 1244)
  - "Nursing in Commerce and Industry" - Circularizing and Distribution, October 20, 1945-September 24, 1953 (Box 106, Folder 1245)
  - "Nursing in Commerce and Industry" - Correspondence - General, August 22, 1940-May 10, 1948 (Box 107, Folder 1246)
  - "Nursing in Commerce and Industry" - Correspondence (H-S), October 1, 1940-July 11, 1951 (Box 107, Folder 1247)
  - "Nursing in Commerce and Industry" - Printing, 1945-1949, 1953 (Box 107, Folder 1248)
  - "Office Management for Health Workers" - Correspondence, May 10, 1940-October 10, 1951 (Box 107, Folder 1249)
  - "Office Management for Health Workers" - Distribution and Printing, 1948-1951, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 1250)
  - "Opportunities for Negroes in Medicine", December 18, 1957-October 23, 1961 (Box 107, Folder 1251)
  - "Organized Home Medical Care in New York City" - Correspondence, May 9, 1955-December 18, 1957 (Box 107, Folder 1252)
  - "Organized Home Medical Care in New York City" - Printing and Sales Promotion, December 8, 1955-April 22, 1957 (Box 107, Folder 1253)
  - "Organizing for a Child Guidance Clinic" - DPD-10, 1930, 1939 (Box 107, Folder 1254)
  - Out of Stock Printed Post Card, November 26, 1946-December 17, 1946 (Box 107, Folder 1255)
  - "Papers of Charles V. Chapin", October 14, 1932-September 13, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 1256)
  - "Papers of Wade Hampton Frost" - Correspondence, 1938-1943, 1958, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 1257)
  - "Papers of Wade Hampton Frost" - Printing, April 14, 1939-January 14, 1949 (Box 108, Folder 1258)
  - "The Patient as a Person", April 8, 1932-June 9, 1966 (Box 108, Folder 1259)
  - "Patients Have Families" - Correspondence, April 9, 1944-July 25, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1260)
  - "Patients Have Families" - Correspondence - Disguises, January 14, 1944-March 24, 1944 (Box 108, Folder 1261)
    Restricted material.
  - "Patients Have Families" - Printing, December 7, 1943-September 11, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 1262)
  - "Pediatric Psychiatry" - Correspondence, Distribution, Editorial, 1962-1963, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 1263)
  - "Pediatric Psychiatry" - Permissions and Production, July 31, 1962-August 14, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 1264)
  - "A Pediatrician in Search of Mental Hygiene", 1932-1938, 1950, 1961 (Box 109, Folder 1265)
  - "Pediatrics and the Emotional Needs of the Child" - Circularizing and Correspondence, October 15, 1947-October 1, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 1266)
  - "Pediatrics and the Emotional Needs of the Child" - Distribution and Printing, March 17, 1948-June 24, 1954 (Box 109, Folder 1267)
  - "Perinatal Mortality in New York City" - Correspondence and Printing, November 6, 1952-May 12, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 1268)
  - "Perinatal Mortality in New York City" - Sales Promotion, January 31, 1955-June 6, 1955 (Box 109, Folder 1269)
  - "Personality and the Cultural Pattern" - Correspondence, 1932-1938, 1951, 1961-1965 (Box 109, Folder 1270)
  - "Personality and the Cultural Pattern" - Editorial, December 2, 1936-May 3, 1937 (Box 109, Folder 1271)
  - "Personality and the Cultural Pattern" - Printing, November 14, 1936-April 5, 1948 (Box 109, Folder 1272)
  - "Physiology of Shock" - Correspondence, 1946-1952, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 1273)
  - "Physiology of Shock" - Permission to Quote, February 24, 1949-September 18, 1950 (Box 110, Folder 1274)
  - "Physiology of Shock" - Printing and Sales Promotion, February 2, 1950-January 3, 1952 (Box 110, Folder 1275)
  - "The Pineal Gland" - Correspondence, October 9, 1953-October 10, 1957 (Box 110, Folder 1276)
  - "The Pineal Gland" - Printing/Production, 1953-1967, 1962 (Box 110, Folder 1277)
  - "The Pineal Gland" - Revision and Sales Promotion, 1954, 1960-1965 (Box 110, Folder 1278)
  - "Plague on Us" - Correspondence - General, January 3, 1940-May 22, 1961 (Box 110, Folder 1279)
  - "Plague on Us" - Correspondence - Manuscript (A-D), February 15, 1935-January 29, 1941 (Box 110, Folder 1280)
  - "Plague on Us" - Correspondence - Manuscript (E-H), May 22, 1935-February 18, 1941 (Box 111, Folder 1281)
  - "Plague on Us" - Correspondence - Manuscript (J-W), February 26, 1935-November 26, 1940 (Box 111, Folder 1282)
  - "Plague on Us" - Printing - First, January 5, 1939-January 25, 1941 (Box 111, Folder 1283)
  - "Plague on Us" - Printing - Second to Fourth, January 14, 1941-May 4, 1953 (Box 111, Folder 1284)
  - "Pneumonia and Serum Therapy", March 1, 1937-March 7, 1938 (Box 111, Folder 1285)
  - "Pneumonia, with Special Reference to Pneumonococcus Lobar Pneumonia", 1931-1939, 1949 (Box 111, Folder 1286)
  - "A Point Scale of Performance Tests," Volume I, January 17, 1928-May 4, 1943 (Box 111, Folder 1287)
  - "A Point Scale of Performance Tests," Volume I - Revised Edition - Correspondence, September 29, 1942-October 24, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 1288)
  - "A Point Scale of Performance Tests," Volume I - Revised Edition - Printing, March 2, 1942-January 24, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 1289)
  - "A Point Scale of Performance Tests," Volume II, April 13, 1931-July 19, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1290)
  - "Postgraduate Instruction of Health Officers and Nurses", October 21, 1935-May 4, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 1291)
  - "The Practical Nurse" - Correspondence, March 5, 1944-September 10, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1292)
  - "The Practical Nurse" - Distribution and Expenses, May 8, 1944-June 10, 1953 (Box 112, Folder 1293)
  - "The Practical Nurse" - Permission to Quote and Printing, December 18, 1944-September 4, 1947 (Box 112, Folder 1294)
  - "Prediction of Vocational Success", December 16, 1932-March 12, 1934 (Box 112, Folder 1295)
  - "Preliminary Report on the conference on Mental Hygiene Aspects of Pediatrics at Hershey", April 2, 1947-June 10, 1947 (Box 112, Folder 1296)
  - "Prevention of Chronic Illness" - Correspondence and Distribution, June 8, 1955-April 17, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 1297)
  - "Prevention of Chronic Illness" - Editorial and Permission to Quote, December 7, 1956-October 1, 1957 (Box 112, Folder 1298)
  - "Prevention of Chronic Illness" - Production and Release Forms, September 27, 1956-June 25, 1957 (Box 112, Folder 1299)
  - Private Mailing Card, December 19-27, 1950 (Box 112, Folder 1300)
  - "The Problem Child at Home", 1925-1929, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 1301)
  - "The Problem Child in School", April 28, 1925-June 19, 1946 (Box 112, Folder 1302)
  - "Prothrombin" - Correspondence and Distribution, October 6, 1959-November 2, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 1303)
  - "Prothrombin" - Editorial, September 22, 1960-February 7, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 1304)
  - "Prothrombin" - Permission to Quote and Production, June 5, 1959-July 2, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 1305)
  - "Psychiatric Clinics for Children" - Correspondence, January 28, 1932-July 11, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 1306)
  - "Psychiatric Clinics for Children" - Printing, September 26, 1939-September 29, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 1307)
  - "Psychiatric Hospital as a Small Society" - Correspondence, June 15, 1954-August 3, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 1308)
  - "Psychiatric Hospital as a Small Society" - Distribution and Editorial, September 26, 1957-March 23, 1960 (Box 113, Folder 1309)
  - "Psychiatric Hospital as a Small Society" - Permission to Quote and Production, August 12, 1957-June 18, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 1310)
  - "Psychiatry in Medical Education", 1936-1950, 1969-1971 (Box 114, Folder 1311)
  - "Psychiatric Interviews with Children" - Correspondence, October 28, 1937-January 4, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 1312)
  - "Psychiatric Interviews with Children" - Correspondence - Clinics, February 10, 1943-August 15, 1946 (Box 114, Folder 1313)
  - "Psychiatric Interviews with Children" - Disguises, May 29, 1945-July 27, 1945 (Box 114, Folder 1314)
  - "Psychiatric Interviews with Children" - Distribution, November 22, 1946-January 8, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 1315)
  - "Psychiatric Interviews with Children" - Expense Account and Permission to Quote, March 3, 1943-February 7, 1946 (Box 114, Folder 1316)
  - "Psychiatric Interviews with Children" - Printing, May 2, 1946-December 16, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 1317)
  - "Psychiatric Social Work" - Correspondence, July 15, 1930-July 11, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1318)
  - "Psychiatric Social Work" - Printing, January 20, 1940-December 16, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 1319)
  - "Psychiatry for the Pediatrician" - Correspondence, 1940-1949, 1961-1963 (Box 114, Folder 1320)
  - "Psychiatry for the Pediatrician" - Distribution - Royalty, April 10, 1947-July 11, 1951 (Box 115, Folder 1321)
  - "Psychological Appraisal of Children with Cerebral Defects" - Correspondence and Distribution, June 6, 1956-June 13, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 1322)
  - "Psychological Appraisal of Children with Cerebral Defects" - Editorial, March 4, 1958-August 31, 1959 (Box 115, Folder 1323)
  - "Psychological Appraisal of Children with Cerebral Defects" - Permission to Quote and Production, April 12, 1958-February 15, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 1324)
  - "Psychomotor Aspects of Mental Illness" - Correspondence, January 12, 1953-February 1, 1957 (Box 115, Folder 1325)
  - "Psychomotor Aspects of Mental Illness" - Production and Sales Promotion, October 9, 1953-October 4, 1954 (Box 115, Folder 1326)
  - "Psychotherapy in General Medicine", May 14, 1946-August 24, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 1327)
  - Public Health Circulars, November 7-17, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 1328)
  - "Public Health is People", June 8, 1949-March 10, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 1329)
  - "Public Health Law", 1937-1940, 1949-1951 (Box 116, Folder 1330)
  - "Public Health Law" - Revised Edition, October 2, 1941-November 19, 1954 (Box 116, Folder 1331)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - Correspondence, November 19, 1931-June 17, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 1332)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - Correspondence, November 19, 1931-June 17, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 1333)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - Correspondence, November 19, 1931-June 17, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 1334)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - Distribution and Expense Account, February 11, 1938-December 19, 1946 (Box 116, Folder 1335)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - Permission to Quote and Printing, April 9, 1940-September 23, 1948 (Box 117, Folder 1336)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - 1951 Revision - Correspondence, October 17, 1944-October 17, 1952 (Box 117, Folder 1337)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - 1951 Revision - Index and Permission to Quote, January 29, 1951-June 14, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 1338)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - 1951 Revision - Printing, October 18, 1950-March 12, 1952 (Box 117, Folder 1339)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - 1951 Revision - Reprinting, October 14, 1954-January 26, 1966 (Box 117, Folder 1340)
  - "The Public Health Nurse and Her Patient" - 1951 Revision - Sales Promotion, June 13, 1951-April 1, 1952 (Box 117, Folder 1341)
  - Publications Lists, June 20, 1949-May 12, 1970 (Box 117, Folder 1342)
  - Publications Lists, June 20, 1949-May 12, 1970 (Box 117, Folder 1343)
  - Publications Lists - Auxiliary, 1951-1966 (Box 117, Folder 1344)
  - "The Purpose and Scope of Visiting Teacher Work", September 17, 1928-May 29, 1930 (Box 117, Folder 1345)
  - "Recording and Reporting for Child Guidance Clinics", September 10, 1929-November 17, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 1346)
  - "Recording of Local Health Work" - Correspondence, April 14, 1933-May 29, 1935 (Box 118, Folder 1347)
  - "Recording of Local Health Work" - Printing, May 17, 1934-February 3, 1950 (Box 118, Folder 1348)
  - "Recording of Local Health Work" - Reprinting, October 6, 1936-November 8, 1946 (Box 118, Folder 1349)
  - "The Red Cell" - Correspondence, August 22, 1960-October 13, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 1350)
  - "The Red Cell" - Distribution and Editorial, November 13, 1961-November 12, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 1351)
  - "The Red Cell" - Permission to Quote, March 1, 1962-September 14, 1962 (Box 118, Folder 1352)
  - "The Red Cell" - Production, September 28, 1961-November 15, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 1353)
  - Removal Notices, January 9-28, 1952 (Box 118, Folder 1354)
  - "Resistance to Tuberculosis" - Correspondence and Distribution, March 15, 1963-September 23, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 1355)
  - "Resistance to Tuberculosis" - Editorial, August 30, 1963-February 15, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 1356)
  - "Resistance to Tuberculosis" - Permission to Quote and Production, July 8, 1963-December 2, 1964 (Box 119, Folder 1357)
  - "Resident Physician's Handbook", July 20, 1931-December 3, 1932 (Box 119, Folder 1358)
  - Review Cards, September 23-30, 1949 (Box 119, Folder 1359)
  - "Rheumatic Fever" - Correspondence - General, December 8, 1931-September 29, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 1360)
  - "Rheumatic Fever" - Correspondence - General, December 8, 1931-September 29, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 1361)
  - "Rheumatic Fever" - Correspondence - Illustrations/Permission to Quote, January 4, 1939-June 20, 1940 (Box 119, Folder 1362)
  - "Rheumatic Fever" - Printing - First, January 14, 1937-August 8, 1940 (Box 119, Folder 1363)
  - "Rheumatic Fever" - Printing - First (E-W), January 18, 1937-June 5, 1940 (Box 119, Folder 1364)
  - "Rheumatic Fever" - Printing - Second, Third and Reprinting, June 6, 1944-March 20, 1946 (Box 119, Folder 1365)
  - "Rheumatoid Arthritis" - Correspondence and Distribution, March 30, 1955-August 15, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 1366)
  - "Rheumatoid Arthritis" - Editorial and Printing, May 7, 1956-September 17, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 1367)
  - "The Rochester Regional Hospital Council" - Correspondence and Printing, November 16, 1954-April 11, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 1368)
  - "The Rochester Regional Hospital Council" - Sales Promotion, January 20, 1956-May 31, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 1369)
  - "Rural Health Practice" - Correspondence, April 2, 1931-April 20, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 1370)
  - "Rural Health Practice" - Correspondence, April 2, 1931-April 20, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 1371)
  - "Rural Health Practice" - Correspondence - Permissions/Royalty, 1936, 1949-1951 (Box 120, Folder 1372)
  - "Rural Health Practice" - Printing, June 26, 1936-September 16, 1947 (Box 120, Folder 1373)
  - Rural Hospital Forms, July 10, 1942-January 25, 1949 (Box 120, Folder 1374)
  - "The School and Mental Health", March 31, 1931-January 16, 1950 (Box 121, Folder 1375)
  - "School Health Services", December 7, 1936-June 27, 1946 (Box 121, Folder 1376)
  - "Serological Fractions in Schizophrenia" - Correspondence and Distribution, October 24, 1961-February 1, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 1377)
  - "Serological Fractions in Schizophrenia" - Editorial and Production, February 13, 1962-August 16, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 1378)
  - "Small Community Hospitals" - Correspondence, November 12, 1932-September 3, 1956 (Box 121, Folder 1379)
  - "Small Community Hospitals" - Printing and Reprinting, November 5, 1943-December 16, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 1380)
  - Smith, Homer - Memorial Volume, November 18, 1963-September 12, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 1381)
  - "Snow on Cholera" - Correspondence, 1936-1937, 1946-1965, 1979-1981 (Box 121, Folder 1382)
  - "Snow on Cholera" - Correspondence, 1936-1937, 1946-1965, 1979-1981 (Box 121, Folder 1383)
  - "Snow on Cholera" - Printing, 1936-1939, 1949-1954 (Box 121, Folder 1384)
  - "Social Medicine: Its Derivations and Objectives" - Correspondence, November 5, 1947-August 9, 1951 (Box 122, Folder 1385)
  - "Social Medicine: Its Derivations and Objectives" - Distribution and Printing, November 10, 1947-February 8, 1951 (Box 122, Folder 1386)
  - "Social Service and Mental Health: A Study of Psychiatric Social Workers", June 4, 1950-June 2, 1953 (Box 122, Folder 1387)
  - "Solving School Health Problems" - Correspondence, October 24, 1939-August 17, 1951 (Box 122, Folder 1388)
  - "Solving School Health Problems" - Printing, February 16, 1942-October 23, 1950 (Box 122, Folder 1389)
  - "Somatosensory Changes After Penetrating Brain Wounds in Man" - Correspondence and Distribution, October 28, 1957-July 22, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 1390)